{
    "subject": "resource/Eric_Feldt",
    "predicate": "property/battles",
    "object": "resource/New_Guinea_campaign",
    "human_readable": "Eric Feldt participated in the New Guinea campaign.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9659326076507568,
            "question": "Are there any historical records about Eric Feldt's involvement in the New Guinea campaign?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.871356725692749,
            "question": "Who participated in the New Guinea campaign?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8612717986106873,
            "question": "What was the name of the campaign Eric Feldt participated in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.572330892086029,
            "question": "Where did the New Guinea campaign take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5518909692764282,
            "question": "In which military campaign did Eric Feldt take part?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47277000546455383,
            "question": "What were the key events of the New Guinea campaign?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4646187424659729,
            "question": "Was Eric Feldt involved in a war effort?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3495337665081024,
            "question": "What type of conflict was the New Guinea campaign part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3238981068134308,
            "question": "Why was the New Guinea campaign significant historically?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18400748074054718,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Eric Feldt's military experience?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eric Feldt participated in the New Guinea campaign.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4061_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why was the New Guinea campaign significant historically?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4061_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of conflict was the New Guinea campaign part of?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4061_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Eric Feldt involved in a war effort?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4061_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4061_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4061_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4061_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4061_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4061_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4061_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4061_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4061_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4061_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4061_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for the given query:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents provided mention Eric Feldt, Commander of the Australian coast watchers, and his involvement with establishing a Coastwatching organisation throughout Papua New Guinea and the Solomon Islands. Although they do not explicitly mention the New Guinea campaign, it is mentioned in document /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4061/re-ranker-msmarco/46.txt that Eric Feldt became warden of the gold fields at Wau in New Guinea and was recalled to active duty when war broke out in Europe, which implies his involvement with operations in New Guinea."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Eric Augustas Feldt OBE, RAN played a significant role in establishing and commanding the coastwatchers organization during World War II. This included operations in both New Guinea and the Solomon Islands. Therefore, it is reasonable to conclude that he participated in the New Guinea campaign."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}